1stslice.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - 1stslice

_Effective as of 03/24/2015._

First Slice Media, LLC (“First Slice”) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to First Slice’s online and mobile website, services, and applications (“Site”), and has established this privacy statement (“Statement”) to inform you of First Slice’s information gathering and dissemination policies and practices regarding your use of the Site.

### 1\. SITE INFORMATION COLLECTION

**_Information Collected_**

As you navigate the Site, First Slice may collect information such as your Internet Protocol address, Web browser information, and your actions while on the Site. This information will be collected, if at all, through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons. Standing alone, this information does not personally identify you. When expressing interest in First Slice’s products or services, you may have the option to provide contact information such as your name, organization name, address, e-mail address, phone number. Providing this optional information is voluntary on your part, and in the absence of providing such information you remain anonymous to First Slice. You may also have the option of engaging in other forms of communication such as online forums or communities, during which First Slice may collect a record of information disclosed by you. If you access the Site on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, First Slice also may collect your unique device identifier and mobile device IP address (e.g. MAC address), as well as information about your device’s operating system, mobile carrier, and mobile Internet browsers, your precise location information, and other information described in this Policy.

**_Use of Information Collected_**

First Slice and its affiliates and business partners may use non-personally identifiable information collected from you to operate and improve the Site, diagnose technical problems, to respond to your request for information, or to send you unsolicited communications about products, services, promotions, partners or events that may interest you. In no event will First Slice share personally-identifiable information, including credit card or other financially-sensitive information, without your consent except in response to legal process, for example in response to a court order or a subpoena, or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request. First Slice also may disclose such information to third parties in connection with fraud-scoring, detection, and prevention activities or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to protect our rights and the rights of others, and as otherwise required by law. In addition, First Slice may transfer information about you in the event of a business transaction, such as if we or one of our business units or our relevant assets are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company.

**_Third Party Links_**

The Site may contain ads served by reputable third parties, co-promotions or sponsors, as well as links to other web sites or third party applications such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn or YouTube. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies. First Slice is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party ad servers, promoters, web sites or applications, and we advise you to refer to the policy statement of these third parties to understand how they collect and use information.

**_International Transfer_**

The Site may be accessible internationally, however our computer systems are currently based in the United States. Therefore, your personally identifiable information will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you access the Site as a visitor from outside the United States, you consent to the collection and/or processing in the United States of your personally identifiable information, which includes the use of cookies as described above.

### 2\. GENERAL PROVIONS APPLICABLE TO ALL VISITORS

**_Sensitive Information_**

We will not intentionally collect or maintain, and do not want you to provide, any information regarding your medical or health condition, race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or other sensitive information.

**_Children’s Online Privacy Protection_**

The Site is not designed for or directed to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

**_Security_**

The Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of information and data under our control. First Slice hosts the Site in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from intruders. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information and data.

**_Verification_**

First Slice utilizes the self-assessment approach to assure its compliance with this Statement. First Slice regularly verifies that the Statement is accurate, comprehensive, prominently displayed, completely implemented and in conformity with the Safe Harbor Principles and conducts its self-assessment on an annual basis to ensure all relevant privacy practices are followed. Appropriate employee training is in place and internal procedures for periodically conducting objective reviews of compliance are in place. A statement verifying this self-assessment is signed by a corporate officer or other authorized representative at least once a year.

**_Opt-Out Policy_**

First Slice offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after providing information, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties, send a request specifying your new choice to:info@firstslicemedia.com.

**_Correcting & Updating Your Information_**

To receive a copy of, or to update information you have provided to, First Slice via the Site, please send an e-mail to: info@firstslicemedia.com. First Slice will respond to your correction or update request within at most thirty (30) days from the date of your request.

**_Changes to this Privacy Statement_**

First Slice reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement as reasonably necessary or advisable to accommodate changes to the law, technology or circumstances, and will use reasonable efforts to provide notification of the material changes through the Site at least thirty (30) business days prior to the changes taking effect.

**_Additional Information_**

Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of the Site should be directed to First Slice’s Security Administrator by e-mailing such questions to: info@firstslicemedia.com or by regular mail addressed to First Slice Media, LLC, Attn: Security Administrator, 6250 Hollywood Blvd., Unit 5A, Los Angeles, CA 90028.

**_Disputes/Arbitration_**

First Slice will attempt to investigate and promptly resolve any disputes or complaint regarding the interpretation or compliance with this Statement. In the event that First Slice is unable to resolve any issues or complaints to your satisfaction, then the dispute, claim or controversy arising out of or relating to this Statement or the breach, termination, enforcement, interpretation or validity thereof, including the determination of the scope or applicability of this Statement to arbitration, shall be determined by arbitration in Los Angeles, California before a single arbitrator. The arbitration shall be administered by JAMS pursuant to its Domestic (or International, as applicable) Comprehensive Arbitration Rules and Procedures. Judgment on the Award may be entered in any court having jurisdiction.

### 3\. Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about what personal information a company shares with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. First Slice does not share your information with third parties for the third parties’ own and independent direct marketing purposes. If you have any questions about what personal information First Slice may share with third parties that are not already answered in this Statement, please contact First Slice at: info@firstslicemedia.com.

### 4\. Do Not Track Requests

Certain browsers have incorporated “Do Not Track” features. Most of these features, when turned on, send a signal or preference to the websites you visit indicating that you do not wish to be tracked. Those sites (or the third-party content on those sites) may continue to engage in activities you might view as tracking even though you have expressed this preference, depending on the sites’ privacy practices. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret the Do Not Track signal, First Slice does not currently respond to the browser Do Not Track signals on its Site.
